#### Siavash Ebrahimi Darsinouei

Dubai - UAE | +971 55 236 4938 | ebrahimi.siavash@gmail.com

## Personal Profile

A forward-thinking professional offering a unique combination of strong business acumen, game development and communication skills. Interested in designing immersive and interactive VR experiences and video games. Strong leadership and problem-solving skills. Fluent in English and Farsi.

### **Education**

Yazd Azad University
B.S. Environmental Studies

May 2004

**Certificates** 

SAE Institute
Game Development
Nov 2021

FORTINET NSE InstituteOnline, DubaiNSE 1 Network Security AssociateAugust 22, 2020NSE 2 Network Security AssociateSeptember 10, 2020

University of Michigan
Introduction to Data Science in Python
2020

Introduction to Data Science in Python
Jun 08,

Applied Plotting, Charting & Data Representation in Python

July 12, 2020

Business Idea Center (BIC) of Tehran

Business Development and Communication.

Jun

2014

Canadian University of DubaiDubai, UAEEnglish for Business CommunicationJuly 2009

#### Work Experience

### **Freelance Unity Developer**

Dubai, UAE

October 2021 – Present

 Designed and developed 3D games and VR environments using multiple tools including Unity, C#, Maya, Adobe Photoshop & Premiere.

# Blue Marine Shipping Business Development Manager Dubai, UAE July 2018 – Present

- Developed and maintained the long-term relationships with the clients, business partners and prospects in the EMEA region.
- Studied the target markets and provided market insights to the sales and marketing teams, supporting their decision-making process.

Account Manager July 2013 – July 2018

• Maintained the relationship with the clients, identified and managed sales lead and upsell opportunities according to the annual sales KPIs.

## Sabz Energy Tejarat Arvand LLC Commercial Advisor

Tehran, Iran & Remote

March 2016 - July 2018

 Provided market analytical insights to support the management team amend and approve the business strategy plans.

### Siavash Ebrahimi Darsinouei

Dubai - UAE | +971 55 236 4938 | ebrahimi.siavash@gmail.com

Fn Touch UAE

# Co-Founder & Commercial Manager

June 2008 - May 2013

• Developed the pricing strategy and managed the financial transactions related to the distribution of a wide range of IoT products.

# **Aryavand Tehran Co.**

Tehran, Iran

Sales and Service Director (Printers Division)

*June* 2004 – May 2008

- Supervised the distribution of large format printers to advertisement firms throughout the country.
- Conducted national training courses regarding the operation and maintenance of large-format printers.

# Languages and Interests

- Languages: English (Fluent), Farsi (Native)
- Interests: Travelling, Music, Movies, Reading